<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<locale xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="l10n_output.xsd" locale="enUS">
  <e id="0">GLOBAL_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="1">GLOBAL_PERMISSION_ERROR</e>
  <e id="2">An error has occurred.</e>
  <e id="3">GLOBAL_BAD_TOKEN</e>
  <e id="4">GLOBAL_NOT_IMPLEMENTED</e>
  <e id="5">An error has occurred.</e>
  <e id="6">GLOBAL_PING_TIMEOUT</e>
  <e id="7">GLOBAL_NEEDS_REPLACEMENT</e>
  <e id="8">GLOBAL_TIMEOUT</e>
  <e id="9">GLOBAL_DUPLICATE_TOKEN</e>
  <e id="10">WAITING</e>
  <e id="11">SHUTTING_DOWN</e>
  <e id="12">CALLBACK_REQUIRED</e>
  <e id="13">GLOBAL_DOWNLOAD_IN_PROGRESS</e>
  <e id="14">In order to access this content, you must upgrade your copy of StarCraft II.</e>
  <e id="15">The selected player is unable to access this feature or map.</e>
  <e id="16">Using StarCraft II: Starter Edition, you are unable to message a player that has not added you as a friend. </e>
  <e id="17">This feature is temporarily unavailable.</e>
  <e id="18">Operation cancelled</e>
  <e id="19">PACKET_SIZE_LIMIT_REACHED</e>
  <e id="20">PACKET_CORRUPT</e>
  <e id="21">BYTECODE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="22">[PH] Data corruption caused a disconnect.</e>
  <e id="100">There was an internal error while connecting to Battle.net. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="101">The authentication module provided by the service is corrupt. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="102">AUTH_NO_BATTLETAGS</e>
  <e id="103">You have attempted to connect to an invalid server. If this problem persists, please contact customer support.</e>
  <e id="104">Your login information was incorrect. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="105">Your connection was closed because you logged out of the client.</e>
  <e id="106">Your login attempt timed-out. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="107">This Battle.net account does not have an associated game account for StarCraft II. This error can occur if you have not purchased the game, or have not yet linked your game account to this Battle.net account.</e>
  <e id="108">INVALID_TOKEN</e>
  <e id="109">You have attempted to log into Battle.net with a program not permitted to connect to the service. If this problem persists, please contact customer service.</e>
  <e id="110">You have attempted to log into Battle.net from an unsupported operating system.</e>
  <e id="111">You are attempting to sign in using a locale descriptor for an unsupported language.</e>
  <e id="112">Game client version mismatch with selected region.

The currently selected region may not yet be updated to the latest version, and you will have to wait until maintenance on this region is complete. You may be able to continue playing if you change back to the region in which you last updated the game.</e>
  <e id="113">There is a temporary outage of the Battle.net service. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="114">Unable to download an authentication module. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="115">You have been disconnected from Battle.net because another computer connected using your account.</e>
  <e id="116">Your login information was incorrect. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="117">AUTH_VERSION_CHECK_SUCCEEDED</e>
  <e id="118">BAD_VERSION_HASH</e>
  <e id="119">AUTH_CANT_RETRIEVE_PORTAL_LIST</e>
  <e id="120">AUTH_DARK_PORTAL_DOES_NOT_EXIST</e>
  <e id="121">AUTH_DARK_PORTAL_FILE_CORRUPTED</e>
  <e id="122">Battle.net is down for maintenance. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="123">You have logged in too soon after being disconnected. Please wait a moment and try again.</e>
  <e id="124">AUTH_USE_GRUNT_LOGON</e>
  <e id="125">You have been disconnected due to inactivity. Please try again when you are ready to play.</e>
  <e id="126">The cache entry for this account is expired.</e>
  <e id="127">IGR Benefactor does not exist.</e>
  <e id="128">Authentication module not found. Please try again later. If this problem persists, please contact customer service.</e>
  <e id="129">Your account is not licensed for this game.</e>
  <e id="130">Stalker could not validate you. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="131">You've attempted to connect to a bad server.  Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="132">The stalker client can't connect to the stalker server. If this error occurs repeatedly, the stalker service may be down.</e>
  <e id="133">You were disconnected from the server.</e>
  <e id="134">The Stalker server didn't give a key to the client to decrypt the game. If this error occurs repeatedly, the stalker service may be down.</e>
  <e id="135">The local stalker client failed to use the key from the server to decrypt the game, which indicates a problem with the key generation or resolution.</e>
  <e id="136">Stalker failed to hand off the key back to the game executable.</e>
  <e id="137">You must accept the agreement in order to continue.</e>
  <e id="138">A new patch is available. The game will now close and apply the patch automatically. You will be able to continue after the patch has been applied.</e>
  <e id="139">This account does not yet have a password associated with it.  Complete the account setup process and try again.</e>
  <e id="140">Your account has no game accounts that can be used in this region. Are you using the correct client?</e>
  <e id="141">Our login system has detected a change in your access pattern. In order to protect the account, we require you to verify your identity via a message sent to the e-mail address associated with this account. For more information, please visit [us.battle.net/account/support/password-reset.html].</e>
  <e id="142">Unable to resume session because logon is from a different computer. Please attempt to log on again.</e>
  <e id="143">Your Battle.net account has not been verified yet. You must verify your account in order to continue. Please go to Battle.net Account Management to start the verification process.</e>
  <e id="144">Your account is only accessible when connecting from a privileged network.</e>
  <e id="145">This Internet Game Room (IGR) is not configured to service this game.</e>
  <e id="146">PH-This account must be unlocked using Phone Secure before you can logon.</e>
  <e id="147">PH-This account must be unlocked using Phone Secure before you can logon. The last recorded Phone Secure unlock was too long ago to be used.</e>
  <e id="148">PH-This account has been locked due to suspicious activity; please use Phone Secure to unlock it.</e>
  <e id="149">PH-This account has been temporary restricted from connecting due to multiple Phone Secure authentication failures; Please wait X minutes before attempting to use Phone Secure unlock again.</e>
  <e id="150">AUTH_NO_COOKIE</e>
  <e id="151">AUTH_COOKIES_DISABLED</e>
  <e id="152">PASSWORD_DISABLED</e>
  <e id="153">Game client version mismatch with selected region.  You may be able to continue playing if you exit the client, patch from the launcher, and restart.</e>
  <e id="154">AUTH_ACCOUNT_UNDERAGE</e>
  <e id="155">AUTH_IDENTITY_CHECK_PENDING</e>
  <e id="156">AUTH_IDENTITY_UNVERIFIED</e>
  <e id="200">An unknown error occurred logging into your game account.</e>
  <e id="201">There is no game account for this Battle.net account. If this problem persists, please contact customer service.</e>
  <e id="202">Your account has been banned due to multiple violations of Battle.net service policies.
Please check your registered email address for more information.</e>
  <e id="203">Your account has been suspended due to multiple violations of Battle.net service policies.
Please check your registered email address for more information.</e>
  <e id="204">Access to your account has been temporarily locked because payment for the product has been cancelled or disputed by the account owner.
Please contact customer support for more information.</e>
  <e id="205">This account is already logged into Battle.net.
Please check the spelling and try again.</e>
  <e id="206">You have used up your prepaid time for this account.
Please visit Battle.net Account Management to purchase more time to continue playing.</e>
  <e id="207">Your game account subscription has expired.
Please visit http://us.battle.net/ to purchase more time.</e>
  <e id="208">Your game account subscription has expired.
Please visit http://us.battle.net/ to purchase more time.</e>
  <e id="209">Access to this account is currently restricted by parental controls. </e>
  <e id="210">Your trial subscription has expired.
Please visit Battle.net Account Management to upgrade your account.</e>
  <e id="211">Your game account is locked by anti-indulgence controls.</e>
  <e id="212">This game account is not of the correct region.</e>
  <e id="213">You have applied a mobile phone lock to your account. You can change your locked status by calling your account lock phone number.</e>
  <e id="214">Access to your account has been temporarily locked because payment for the product has been cancelled or disputed by the user. Please contact customer support for more information.</e>
  <e id="215">In order to log in to this game using IGR time, this game account must first be merged with a Battle.net account.</e>
  <e id="216">This game account has been locked but can be unlocked by customer service.</e>
  <e id="217">Your game account is only able to play from an authorized Internet Game Room (IGR).</e>
  <e id="218">The payment method on this account has changed, please login again.</e>
  <e id="219">Could not load payment method, please add time and log in again.</e>
  <e id="220">This game account is in an invalid state, please contact customer support.</e>
  <e id="300">CHANNEL_INDEX_TOO_HIGH</e>
  <e id="301">Maximum number of channels open.</e>
  <e id="302">The channel does not exist.</e>
  <e id="303">You were unable to join the channel because the system still thinks that you are in it. If this persists, log out and try again.</e>
  <e id="304">The chat channel is full.</e>
  <e id="305">You do not have permission to create or join that channel.</e>
  <e id="306">The system is currently not able to service channels. Wait a minute and then try again.</e>
  <e id="307">Invalid invite target.</e>
  <e id="308">CHANNEL_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="309">You are already in the requested channel.</e>
  <e id="310">Channel cannot be found.</e>
  <e id="311">Network error.</e>
  <e id="312">Your current channel will be replaced by another channel.</e>
  <e id="313">No channel by that name exists.</e>
  <e id="314">The player is already in the channel.</e>
  <e id="315">The moderator has removed you from the channel.</e>
  <e id="316">You are not currently in a channel.</e>
  <e id="317">%s has declined your invitation.</e>
  <e id="318">%s is not online.</e>
  <e id="319">%s is currently blocked and cannot be invited.</e>
  <e id="320">%s has the maximum number of chat windows open.</e>
  <e id="321">The message is too long.</e>
  <e id="322">The message is not valid.</e>
  <e id="323">Your current client program is unable to join this conversation.</e>
  <e id="324">This conversation is restricted by your region.</e>
  <e id="325">There was an error saving some of your channel state.  Some channels may be missing from your recently joined list the next time you log in.</e>
  <e id="326">There was an error saving some of your channel state.  Some channels may not be automatically joined the next time you log in.</e>
  <e id="327">The selected name contains text that is considered inappropriate for a channel name.</e>
  <e id="328">Guest Pass accounts may not join chat channels.</e>
  <e id="329">There is no cow level.</e>
  <e id="330">You may not join any more public channels without first leaving one of your existing channels.</e>
  <e id="331">The number of messages that can be sent to this channel is limited. Please wait to send another message.</e>
  <e id="332">The player you are trying to whisper is not currently accepting messages from players who are not on their friends list.</e>
  <e id="333">The player you are trying to invite is not currently accepting invites from players who are not on their friends list.</e>
  <e id="334">The player you are trying to invite is using an incompatible program.</e>
  <e id="335">This account is not allowed to communicate with other players.</e>
  <e id="336">You must upgrade in order to chat in chat channels.</e>
  <e id="337">You are currently blocking messages from this player and may not communicate with them.</e>
  <e id="400">Character creation failed for unknown reason.</e>
  <e id="401">The character name you selected is not available.</e>
  <e id="402">Maximum number of characters reached.</e>
  <e id="403">There was an unknown error selecting another character.</e>
  <e id="404">The character you selected does not exist. If this problem persists, please contact customer service.</e>
  <e id="405">The region that you tried to create the character on is invalid.</e>
  <e id="406">Character name contains a prohibited word. Please enter a different name.</e>
  <e id="407">Character name contains mature language. Please enter a different name.</e>
  <e id="408">This character has been banned.</e>
  <e id="409">Keyword name contains a prohibited word. Please enter a different name.</e>
  <e id="410">Keyword name contains mature language. Please enter a different name.</e>
  <e id="411">There is already a character with this name.  Please enter a different name.</e>
  <e id="412">Keyword invalid.  Please select a different keyword.</e>
  <e id="413">One of the characters in the name is invalid in this region.</e>
  <e id="414">BAD_PROGRAM</e>
  <e id="415">Your character has been renamed.</e>
  <e id="416">Your character is not flagged to be renamed.</e>
  <e id="417">Your character rename failed. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="500">PROFILE_RECORD_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="501">PROFILE_TIMEOUT</e>
  <e id="502">Connection failed. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="503">PROFILE_WRONG_PYLON</e>
  <e id="504">PROFILE_DOES_NOT_VALIDATE</e>
  <e id="505">PROFILE_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="506">PROFILE_DATABASE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="507">PROFILE_DATABASE_NO_RESULTS</e>
  <e id="508">PROFILE_UNSUPPORTED_ADDRESS_QUERY</e>
  <e id="509">WRONG_RECORD_TYPE</e>
  <e id="510">Cannot get proxy record for profile address.</e>
  <e id="511">Outdated version of profile found.</e>
  <e id="512">This player has no saved campaign data</e>
  <e id="513">The partition set is invalid.</e>
  <e id="514">Invalid record ID provided in request.</e>
  <e id="600">Unable to find this friend.</e>
  <e id="601">FRIEND_INVITE_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="602">FRIEND_ADD_COMPLETED</e>
  <e id="603">FRIEND_INVITE_FAILED</e>
  <e id="604">%s is already your friend.</e>
  <e id="605">FRIEND_REMOVE_FAILED</e>
  <e id="606">FRIEND_REMOVE_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="607">FRIEND_NOTE_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="608">FRIEND_NOTE_FAILED</e>
  <e id="609">FRIEND_BLOCK_ADD_ACCOUNT_FAILED</e>
  <e id="610">FRIEND_BLOCK_ADD_ACCOUNT_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="611">FRIEND_BLOCK_ADD_TOON_FAILED</e>
  <e id="612">FRIEND_BLOCK_ADD_TOON_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="613">FRIEND_BLOCK_REMOVE_ACCOUNT_FAILED</e>
  <e id="614">FRIEND_BLOCK_REMOVE_ACCOUNT_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="615">FRIEND_BLOCK_REMOVE_TOON_FAILED</e>
  <e id="616">FRIEND_BLOCK_REMOVE_TOON_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="617">Adding yourself as a friend is not allowed.</e>
  <e id="618">You have reached the maximum number of Real ID friends and cannot add more Real ID friends or receive friend requests. To make room for other friends, you will have to remove Real ID friends or respond to pending friend requests.</e>
  <e id="619">Could not invite friend because that user has blocked your account in their settings.</e>
  <e id="620">That friend is offline.</e>
  <e id="621">Could not invite friend because your friend's Friends List is currently full.</e>
  <e id="622">Could not invite friend because your friend has too many unanswered invitations.</e>
  <e id="623">You could not invite this friend because you have blocked that player.</e>
  <e id="624">Invalid email address.</e>
  <e id="625">Email address is too short.</e>
  <e id="626">Email address is too long.</e>
  <e id="627">The message is too long.</e>
  <e id="628">Username is too short.</e>
  <e id="629">Username is too long.</e>
  <e id="630">Password is too short.</e>
  <e id="631">Password is too long.</e>
  <e id="632">BAD_PRESENCE_ID</e>
  <e id="633">Cannot add to block list because list is full.</e>
  <e id="634">The message is not valid.</e>
  <e id="635">Could not accept friend invite because your friend cannot have any more friends.</e>
  <e id="636">FRIEND_INVITED_ALREADY</e>
  <e id="637">Could not accept friend invite because your friend has disabled friendships.</e>
  <e id="638">You may not add friends using the BattleTag feature until you have set up a BattleTag yourself. Go to www.Battle.net to set up your BattleTag.</e>
  <e id="700">You have not been invited to this party.</e>
  <e id="701">There has been an internal error.</e>
  <e id="702">You can't do that right now as the party is in a frozen state.</e>
  <e id="703">The party has been disbanded.</e>
  <e id="704">The party is full.</e>
  <e id="705">Could not locate the player.</e>
  <e id="706">The player is already in a party.</e>
  <e id="707">The player is already in the matchmaking queue and cannot join a party.</e>
  <e id="708">The player is already in a game and cannot join a party.</e>
  <e id="709">The player cannot join any more channels.</e>
  <e id="710">The player is ignoring you.</e>
  <e id="711">There was an error in reaching the other player.</e>
  <e id="712">Joined another party.</e>
  <e id="713">Member has left the party.</e>
  <e id="714">The player is about to join a game or has received a game invite and is unable to add people to the party.</e>
  <e id="715">The party leader removed you from the party.</e>
  <e id="716">INCOMPATIBLE_PROGRAM</e>
  <e id="717">[PH] At least one of your party members is using a trial client, and thus you cannot join Quick Match.</e>
  <e id="718">The player you are trying to invite is not currently accepting invites from players who are not on their friends list.</e>
  <e id="2000">Database failure.</e>
  <e id="2001">No result found in database.</e>
  <e id="2002">DATABASE_NULL_RESULT</e>
  <e id="2003">DATABASE_UNEXPECTED_RESULT</e>
  <e id="2004">DATABASE_DROPPED</e>
  <e id="2005">DATABASE_INVALID_ROW_COUNT</e>
  <e id="2006">DATABASE_INVALID_COLUMN_COUNT</e>
  <e id="2007">DATABASE_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="2008">DATABASE_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="2009">DATABASE_EXPIRED_IN_QUEUE</e>
  <e id="2010">DATABASE_CANCELED_IN_QUEUE</e>
  <e id="3000">Map download failed.</e>
  <e id="3001">CREEP_CACHE_HANDLE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3002">CREEP_NO_PREV_GAME_DATA</e>
  <e id="3003">QUEUE_LOOKUP_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3004">CREEP_UNKNOWN</e>
  <e id="3100">ATTRIBCACHE_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3101">ATTRIBCACHE_UNKNOWN_MAP</e>
  <e id="3102">ATTRIBCACHE_UNKNOWN_MMQ</e>
  <e id="3103">ATTRIBCACHE_UNKNOWN_MMQ_TEMPLATE</e>
  <e id="3104">ATTRIBCACHE_SAVE_FAIL</e>
  <e id="3105">ATTRIBCACHE_CORRUPT_MAP</e>
  <e id="3106">ATTRIBCACHE_CANCELLED</e>
  <e id="3107">ATTRIBCACHE_INVALID_MAPLINK</e>
  <e id="3108">ATTRIBCACHE_TOO_MANY_DEPENDENCIES</e>
  <e id="3109">ATTRIBCACHE_BUFFER_DISAPPEARED</e>
  <e id="3110">ATTRIBCACHE_HEADER_SIZE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3111">ATTRIBCACHE_HEADER_CORRUPT</e>
  <e id="3112">ATTRIBCACHE_HEADER_WRONG_VERSION</e>
  <e id="3113">ATTRIBCACHE_NO_MORE_SAVEIDS</e>
  <e id="3114">There was a temporary error fulfilling your request, try again in a few moments.</e>
  <e id="3115">ATTRIBCACHE_MAPS_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="3116">ATTRIBCACHE_MASTER_DISCONNECTED</e>
  <e id="3117">A problem occurred while loading the map.</e>
  <e id="3118">ATTRIBCACHE_NAMESPACE_STILL_IN_USE</e>
  <e id="3119">The given map cannot be played using optional mods.</e>
  <e id="3120">ATTRIBCACHE_NO_PRIMARY_HANDLE</e>
  <e id="3200">File could not be opened.</e>
  <e id="3201">Unable to save header file.</e>
  <e id="3202">File not found in cache.</e>
  <e id="3203">Header file is too small or too large.</e>
  <e id="3204">Internal Battle.net error.</e>
  <e id="3205">Header file is corrupt.</e>
  <e id="3206">Header file is not using the correct version.</e>
  <e id="3207">Publishing only allowed from the client.</e>
  <e id="3208">Publishing only allowed from the server.</e>
  <e id="3209">Publish version is not correct.</e>
  <e id="3210">Unable to verify identifier.</e>
  <e id="3211">A required Battle.net service is not available. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="3212">Error while publishing map.</e>
  <e id="3213">Client logged off.</e>
  <e id="3214">Favorite list could not be found.</e>
  <e id="3215">Recently Played list could not be found.</e>
  <e id="3216">Request not supported.</e>
  <e id="3217">Search string too short.</e>
  <e id="3218">Map not found. It may have been removed.</e>
  <e id="3219">Map cannot be found or author name is incorrect.</e>
  <e id="3220">Unlinked map cannot be re-linked.</e>
  <e id="3221">The 'Show Real Name' option cannot be disabled.</e>
  <e id="3222">Your map  names list is empty.</e>
  <e id="3223">Your map name cannot be blank.</e>
  <e id="3224">Localized map name taken by another map.</e>
  <e id="3225">Publish names must match the previous version for all locales.</e>
  <e id="3226">Cannot publish: not enough space available.</e>
  <e id="3227">Cannot publish: not enough slots available.</e>
  <e id="3228">Cannot publish: not enough slots, not enough space available.</e>
  <e id="3229">Your namespace has not been reserved.</e>
  <e id="3230">Using incorrect namespace.</e>
  <e id="3231">Author does not exist.</e>
  <e id="3232">Public mods cannot be locked.</e>
  <e id="3233">Cannot create game on older version of map. Try creating a game on a more recent version, if available.</e>
  <e id="3234">Could not resolve document info.</e>
  <e id="3235">Cannot publish: the map size is too large.</e>
  <e id="3236">Validation process was cancelled.</e>
  <e id="3237">Validation process timed out. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="3238">A required Battle.net service is not available for validation. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="3239">Namespace does not match previous versions.</e>
  <e id="3240">Header information is missing.</e>
  <e id="3241">Header information is corrupt.</e>
  <e id="3242">Localized text file is missing.</e>
  <e id="3243">Localized text file is too large.</e>
  <e id="3244">Localized text file is corrupt.</e>
  <e id="3245">Dependencies could not be validated.</e>
  <e id="3246">Scope information could not be validated.</e>
  <e id="3247">Attribute definitions could not be validated.</e>
  <e id="3248">Score result definitions could not be validated.</e>
  <e id="3249">Default attribute values could not be validated.</e>
  <e id="3250">Score screen information could not be validated.</e>
  <e id="3251">Variant definitions could not be validated.</e>
  <e id="3252">No variants have been defined.</e>
  <e id="3253">Core dependency is missing.</e>
  <e id="3254">This account is not authorized to access this feature.</e>
  <e id="3255">Label information could not be verified.</e>
  <e id="3256">Dependency must use a fixed version.</e>
  <e id="3257">Multiple versions of the same dependency are used.</e>
  <e id="3258">Too many attribute definitions.</e>
  <e id="3259">Too many score result definitions.</e>
  <e id="3260">Custom attribute definitions may not be used.</e>
  <e id="3261">Publishing is not enabled.</e>
  <e id="3262">Custom maps are not allowed.</e>
  <e id="3263">Custom games are not allowed.</e>
  <e id="3264">A variant specifies a User controller.</e>
  <e id="3265">You must specify at least a valid name for the map.</e>
  <e id="3266">You must have at least one Game Variant defined.</e>
  <e id="3267">VALIDATION_WORKING_SET_MISSING_REQUIRED_ATTRIBUTES</e>
  <e id="3268">VALIDATION_WORKING_SET_CIRCULAR_ATTRIBUTE_DEFINITIONS</e>
  <e id="3269">Editor is using a map name it didn't reserve.</e>
  <e id="3270">You have tried to remove from your favorites a map that is not currently marked as a favorite.</e>
  <e id="3271">You have tried to favorite a map that is already on your list.</e>
  <e id="3272">Retrieving favorites failed, as you are currently exiting the service.</e>
  <e id="3273">You have reached the maximum number of favorites and must remove some before adding more.</e>
  <e id="3274">A temporary error has occurred trying to update your map favorites.  Please try again in a short while.</e>
  <e id="3275">You have submitted a map that has its required permissions modified, which is not currently allowed.</e>
  <e id="3276">You do not have all the permissions that this map requires.</e>
  <e id="3277">You cannot publish an Arcade map that allows optional mods.</e>
  <e id="3278">You cannot be a cluster and a member of a cluster at the same time.</e>
  <e id="3279">There was a temporary error trying to publish your map. Try again later.</e>
  <e id="3280">You cannot publish into another author's map cluster.</e>
  <e id="3281">Your map name contains invalid characters.</e>
  <e id="3282">Your map name cannot begin with whitespace.</e>
  <e id="3283">Your map name cannot end with whitespace.</e>
  <e id="3284">Your map name cannot contain consecutive whitespace.</e>
  <e id="3285">This account is not allowed to publish maps to the service.</e>
  <e id="3286">S2MAP_MAP_FAVORITE_PLEASE_WAIT</e>
  <e id="3287">The game could not be created as specified.</e>
  <e id="3288">A file cannot be an extension-mod without first being marked as a mod.</e>
  <e id="3289">Extension mods cannot be published to the Arcade.</e>
  <e id="3290">Game must use maps and mods from the same program.</e>
  <e id="3300">GATEWAY_REGION_MISMATCH</e>
  <e id="3301">GATEWAY_USAGE_MISMATCH</e>
  <e id="3302">GATEWAY_PROCESS_CANCELLED</e>
  <e id="3303">GATEWAY_FILE_APPEND_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3304">GATEWAY_HASH_MISMATCH</e>
  <e id="3305">GATEWAY_FILE_DELETE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3306">GATEWAY_TOO_MUCH_DATA</e>
  <e id="3307">GATEWAY_FILE_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="3308">GATEWAY_FILE_OPEN_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3309">GATEWAY_FILE_SIZE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3310">GATEWAY_FILE_READ_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3311">GATEWAY_FILE_RENAME_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3312">GATEWAY_FILE_CORRUPT</e>
  <e id="3313">GATEWAY_TASK_CASE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3314">GATEWAY_REPLAY_CHUNK_MISSING</e>
  <e id="3315">There was a temporary error with your request. Please try again in a few minutes.</e>
  <e id="3316">You must select a character before you can complete this action.</e>
  <e id="3317">You do not have permission to complete this publish.</e>
  <e id="3318">Error publishing game stats to character profile.</e>
  <e id="3319">GATEWAY_PROCEED</e>
  <e id="3320">GATEWAY_PUBLISH_INVALID_TYPE</e>
  <e id="3321">GATEWAY_PUBLISH_FILEIDS_MUST_BE_UNIQUE</e>
  <e id="3322">Either the publish list never existed or publish failed at an earlier step and got cleaned up.</e>
  <e id="3323">GATEWAY_CLIENT_NOT_CONNECTED</e>
  <e id="3324">GATEWAY_PUBLISH_ABORTED</e>
  <e id="3325">GATEWAY_ANOTHER_FILE_FAILED</e>
  <e id="3326">GATEWAY_CURL_RESULT_SUCCESS</e>
  <e id="3327">GATEWAY_CURL_RESULT_PENDING</e>
  <e id="3328">GATEWAY_CURL_RESULT_PENDING</e>
  <e id="3329">GATEWAY_CURL_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3330">GATEWAY_CURL_BAD_URL</e>
  <e id="3331">GATEWAY_CURL_RESULT_COULD_NOT_WRITE_FILE</e>
  <e id="3332">GATEWAY_CURL_RESULT_CONNECTION_FAILED</e>
  <e id="3333">GATEWAY_CURL_RESULT_TIMEOUT</e>
  <e id="3334">GATEWAY_CURL_HTTP_FAILED</e>
  <e id="3335">GATEWAY_CURL_HTTP_FILE_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="3400">S2GAME_SERVER_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3401">That game is no longer available.</e>
  <e id="3402">The game is currently full or no longer available.</e>
  <e id="3403">The game does not have enough slots to fit your party or is no longer available.</e>
  <e id="3404">S2GAME_SLOT_NOT_RESERVED</e>
  <e id="3405">S2GAME_DISCONNECTED</e>
  <e id="3406">S2GAME_CORRUPT_WORKING_SET</e>
  <e id="3407">S2GAME_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3408">S2GAME_PLAYER_NOT_CONNECTED</e>
  <e id="3409">S2GAME_KICKED_BY_HOST</e>
  <e id="3410">S2GAME_BAD_MAP_NAME</e>
  <e id="3411">S2GAME_CLIENT_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="3412">The player has declined your invitation.</e>
  <e id="3413">No game results found.</e>
  <e id="3414">S2GAME_RESULT_DEFLIST_CORRUPT</e>
  <e id="3415">S2GAME_RESULT_INSTLIST_CORRUPT</e>
  <e id="3416">S2GAME_UNKNOWN_SUMMARY_VERSION</e>
  <e id="3417">S2GAME_SUMMARY_FILE_CORRUPT</e>
  <e id="3418">Game has already started</e>
  <e id="3419">The results of this game are not persistent.</e>
  <e id="3420">There was an error attempting to persistent the results of this game.</e>
  <e id="3421">No rejoin is available.</e>
  <e id="3422">Already connected to a game, rejoin failed.</e>
  <e id="3500">S2MASTER_UNKNOWN_MMQ_HANDLE</e>
  <e id="3501">S2MASTER_MMQ_CLIENT_REMOVED</e>
  <e id="3502">S2MASTER_SERVER_ERROR_INVALID_DATA</e>
  <e id="3503">That game is no longer available.</e>
  <e id="3504">S2MASTER_TEMPLATE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3505">No servers are currently available. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="3506">There was a temporary problem with your request. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="3507">S2MASTER_CLIENT_LOGGED_OFF</e>
  <e id="3508">S2MASTER_PARTY_DISBANDED</e>
  <e id="3509">S2MASTER_PARTY_MODIFIED</e>
  <e id="3510">You cannot join a game because one of your party members is offline.</e>
  <e id="3511">S2MASTER_DATABASE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3512">You cannot create a game because you are in a party and not the party leader.</e>
  <e id="3513">You cannot create a game because your status has been locked.</e>
  <e id="3514">You cannot join a game because you are in a party and not the party leader.</e>
  <e id="3515">You cannot join a game because your status has been locked.</e>
  <e id="3516">You cannot enter the matchmaking queue because your status has been locked.</e>
  <e id="3517">You cannot create a game because you are already in a game.</e>
  <e id="3518">Could not join the matchmaking queue because not all the party members are online.</e>
  <e id="3519">Could not join the matchmaking queue because you are already in a queue.</e>
  <e id="3520">Could not join the matchmaking queue because game creation failed.</e>
  <e id="3521">The requested player does not exist or is not online.</e>
  <e id="3522">Could not leave the matchmaking queue as game creation is in progress.</e>
  <e id="3523">The header is the wrong size for the matchmaking queue.</e>
  <e id="3524">The header is corrupt for the matchmaking queue.</e>
  <e id="3525">Your header version is not compatible with the matchmaking queue.</e>
  <e id="3526">Could not read the header file.</e>
  <e id="3527">The selected matchmaking queue is not active.</e>
  <e id="3528">The selected matchmaking queue has been stopped.</e>
  <e id="3529">The game server timed out when creating the game.</e>
  <e id="3530">The player has already been invited to a game.</e>
  <e id="3531">The player is currently unable to receive game invites.</e>
  <e id="3532">Only the party leader can create a custom game.</e>
  <e id="3533">Only the party leader can join a custom game.</e>
  <e id="3534">The person you are inviting is in a party but is not the party leader. Only party leaders can accept invites.</e>
  <e id="3535">You must exit score screen chat before you can join another game.</e>
  <e id="3536">The player's current party is too large to join this game.</e>
  <e id="3537">You cannot invite yourself to your own game.</e>
  <e id="3538">The player is already in a game or matchmaking queue.</e>
  <e id="3539">The player's party contains an offline member.</e>
  <e id="3540">A party member is missing rating information for a game formed through matchmaking.</e>
  <e id="3541">The selected player is blocking you and cannot be invited to a game.</e>
  <e id="3542">You are asking for Custom Games Lists searches too frequently.</e>
  <e id="3543">You are not currently in the practice league.</e>
  <e id="3544">You have already submitted a self evaluation.</e>
  <e id="3545">You cannot invite a real-life friend without a character.</e>
  <e id="3546">Your game version is outdated.  You must apply the recent game patch before playing a multiplayer game.</e>
  <e id="3547">The chosen map is not available to play.</e>
  <e id="3548">INCOMPATIBLE_PROGRAM</e>
  <e id="3549">You cannot play in this game because you are not on the correct realm.</e>
  <e id="3550">One or more members of your party are running an outdated version of the game and must apply the recent patch before playing a multiplayer game.</e>
  <e id="3551">MASTER_DOWN</e>
  <e id="3552">S2GAME_DOWN</e>
  <e id="3553">The game cannot be created.</e>
  <e id="3554">The map cannot be found.</e>
  <e id="3555">No suitable game could be found. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="3556">The player you are trying to invite is not currently accepting invites from players who are not on their friends list.</e>
  <e id="3557">Your game search has been cancelled due to a service update.</e>
  <e id="3558">Too many matchmaker queues were returned for this query.</e>
  <e id="3559">We are currently rolling over to a new season. The Quickmatch service will return shortly. Get ready for action!</e>
  <e id="3560">Map processing failed.</e>
  <e id="3561">Failed to verify replay file status due to an internal service error. Try again later.</e>
  <e id="3562">Failed to upload replay file due to a temporary service error. Try again shortly.</e>
  <e id="3563">Rejoin has been disabled.</e>
  <e id="3564">You cannot rejoin this game while locked.</e>
  <e id="3565">You cannot enter matchmaking while currently in a game.</e>
  <e id="3566">You cannot enter matchmaking while a member of your party is in a game.</e>
  <e id="3567">Missing required game site information.</e>
  <e id="3568">You cannot enter this matchmaking queue because you do not meet the requirements.</e>
  <e id="3569">You cannot enter this matchmaking queue because not everyone in your party meets the requirements.</e>
  <e id="3570">You cannot enter this queue because you have recently disconected from a game. You must first play a game in Quick Match Mode without disconnecting.</e>
  <e id="3571">You cannot enter this queue because someone in your party has recently disconected from a game. You must first play a game in Quick Match Mode without disconnecting.</e>
  <e id="3572">You cannot enter this queue with a Ranked Play team.</e>
  <e id="3573">You cannot enter Team League without selecting a team.</e>
  <e id="3574">You must enter this queue with a full party of 5 teammates.</e>
  <e id="3575">No game sites were available to start a game.  Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="3600">You own the maximum number of %2$s allowed.</e>
  <e id="3601">You are a member of the maximum number of %2$s allowed.</e>
  <e id="3602">That name is already in use.</e>
  <e id="3603">That clan tag is already in use.</e>
  <e id="3604">That player is already a member.</e>
  <e id="3605">The specified member was not found.</e>
  <e id="3606">The member data has been modified. Please refresh your screen and try again.</e>
  <e id="3607">The player is not a member of this %1$s.</e>
  <e id="3608">The group was not found.</e>
  <e id="3609">The group is full.</e>
  <e id="3610">You do not have permission to perform this action.</e>
  <e id="3611">There are too many entries in this section.</e>
  <e id="3612">The entry was not found.</e>
  <e id="3613">The text does match the requirements.</e>
  <e id="3614">An unexpected error occured.</e>
  <e id="3615">You must transfer ownership to another member before leaving this %1$s.</e>
  <e id="3616">ENTRY_EXISTS</e>
  <e id="3617">This account is not allowed to create groups.</e>
  <e id="3618">There is a pending action of that type.</e>
  <e id="3619">That name is too long.</e>
  <e id="3700">ADVERTCACHE_UNKNOWN_MMQ</e>
  <e id="3701">ADVERTCACHE_MASTER_DISCONNECTED</e>
  <e id="3800">The system is shutting down in %d |4(minute,minutes).</e>
  <e id="3801">The system is shutting down in %d |4(second,seconds).</e>
  <e id="3802">The system is shutting down now.</e>
  <e id="3803">There is a new patch available.  Please log out and download the new patch.</e>
  <e id="3900">FILE_OPEN_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3901">FILE_READ_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3902">FILE_PARSE_ERROR</e>
  <e id="3903">FILE_COMPRESSEDFILE_CORRUPT</e>
  <e id="4000">CLIENTSIDECACHE_LOAD_CANCELLED</e>
  <e id="4001">CLIENTSIDECACHE_LOAD_FILE_NOT_PRESENT</e>
  <e id="4002">CLIENTSIDECACHE_LOAD_UNABLE_TO_OPEN_FILE</e>
  <e id="4003">CLIENTSIDECACHE_LOAD_READ_FAILED</e>
  <e id="4004">CLIENTSIDECACHE_LOAD_DECOMPRESS_FAILED</e>
  <e id="4005">That file is too big.</e>
  <e id="4006">CLIENTSIDECACHE_LOAD_BAD_HASH</e>
  <e id="4007">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_CANCELLED</e>
  <e id="4008">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_BAD_URL</e>
  <e id="4009">There is a problem with the download cache. Please restart the game and try again.</e>
  <e id="4010">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_FILE_NOT_LOCAL</e>
  <e id="4011">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_CONNECTION_FAILED</e>
  <e id="4012">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_TIMEOUT</e>
  <e id="4013">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_BAD_HASH</e>
  <e id="4014">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_HTTP_FILE_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="4015">An error has occurred while attempting to download necessary content. Please check your Internet connection and try again.</e>
  <e id="4016">CLIENTSIDECACHE_READ_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="4017">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_CANCELLED</e>
  <e id="4018">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_UNABLE_TO_OPEN_FILE</e>
  <e id="4019">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_READ_FAILED</e>
  <e id="4020">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_COULD_NOT_CONNECT_TO_GATEWAY</e>
  <e id="4021">Connection to publishing service has been interrupted. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="4022">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_SUNKEN_DENIED</e>
  <e id="4023">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_GATEWAY_DENIED</e>
  <e id="4024">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_FILE_TOO_BIG</e>
  <e id="4025">CLIENTSIDECACHE_WRITE_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="4026">CLIENTSIDECACHE_INDEX_CANCELLED</e>
  <e id="4027">CLIENTSIDECACHE_INDEX_FAILED</e>
  <e id="4028">CLIENTSIDECACHE_DELETE_FAILED</e>
  <e id="4029">CLIENTSIDECACHE_PUBLISH_INVALID_SERVER_DATA</e>
  <e id="4100">The specified ladder does not exist.</e>
  <e id="4101">The object is not ranked on the specified ladder.</e>
  <e id="4102">There was an error fulfilling your request.</e>
  <e id="4103">Removing yourself from a ladder is not currently allowed.</e>
  <e id="4104">The team you are trying to remove no longer exists.</e>
  <e id="4105">There was an error removing you from the ladder. Please try again in a few minutes.</e>
  <e id="4106">Your previous ladder removal request is still processing. Please wait for that to complete and try again.</e>
  <e id="4200">Reward information is currently unavailable for entry.</e>
  <e id="4201">UNLOCKABLE_DEFAULT_UNAVAILABLE</e>
  <e id="4202">A default portrait is not available for entry.</e>
  <e id="4203">Rewards are being updated. Try again.</e>
  <e id="4204">You must earn this reward before you can select it.</e>
  <e id="4205">UPDATE_STILL_IN_PROGRESS</e>
  <e id="4206">FILE_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="4300">The specified league does not exist.</e>
  <e id="4301">The specified season is not valid.</e>
  <e id="4302">The specified division does not exist.</e>
  <e id="4400">Could not retrieve Achievement data. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="4401">NOT_SUBSCRIPTION_LISTENER</e>
  <e id="4402">PROFILE_ADDRESS_NOT_CACHED</e>
  <e id="4403">STATIC_DATA_NOT_LOADED</e>
  <e id="4404">UNKNOWN_PROGRAM</e>
  <e id="4405">LISTENER_NO_PROGRAMS_SPECIFIED</e>
  <e id="4406">NOT_EARNED</e>
  <e id="4407">ALREADY_EARNED</e>
  <e id="4408">CHEAT_CANNOT_REDUCE_CRITERIA</e>
  <e id="4409">Achievement is not available for your region.  Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="4410">UNKNOWN_ID</e>
  <e id="4411">QUEST_ALREADY_ACTIVATED</e>
  <e id="4412">TOON_ACCOUNT_INFO_NOT_CACHED</e>
  <e id="4500">NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="4501">INVALID</e>
  <e id="4600">Facebook returned an unknown error while accessing your account.</e>
  <e id="4601">The Facebook add friend service is unavailable right now. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="4602">USER_USAGE_RESTRICTED</e>
  <e id="4603">The add friend service is unavailable right now. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="4604">USER_PERMISSION_DENIED</e>
  <e id="4605">The login details you entered are incorrect. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="4606">You are no longer connected to Facebook. Please sign in again.</e>
  <e id="4607">NOT_LOGGED_IN</e>
  <e id="4700">MODULE_DISABLED</e>
  <e id="4701">NO_DECISION_TREE</e>
  <e id="4702">HISTORY_ERROR</e>
  <e id="4703">NO_HISTORY</e>
  <e id="4704">DECISION_ERROR</e>
  <e id="4705">WHITELIST_ACTIVE</e>
  <e id="4800">SEASONROLL_UNKNOWN_ERROR</e>
  <e id="4801">TEMPLATE_LOAD_FAILED</e>
  <e id="4802">UNKNOWN_MMQ_KEY</e>
  <e id="4803">FAILED_TO_GENERATE_HEADER_FROM_TEMPLATE</e>
  <e id="4804">FAILED_TO_GENERATE_PROFILE</e>
  <e id="4805">FAILED_TO_ENCODE_HEADER</e>
  <e id="4806">FAILED_TO_WRITE_MATCHMAKER_TO_DEPOT</e>
  <e id="4807">FAILED_TO_CREATE_MATCHMAKER</e>
  <e id="4808">FAILED_TO_UPDATE_MATCHMAKER_PROFILE</e>
  <e id="4900">REVIEWS_MARK_EXISTS</e>
  <e id="4901">This review has been deleted.</e>
  <e id="5000">CACHE_DEPOT_INSERT_FAILURE</e>
  <e id="5001">Something bad happened. Check the logs for more info.</e>
  <e id="5002">The object requested is too big to store in the server</e>
  <e id="5003">The key already exists in the server. If you have supplied a CAS then the key exists with a CAS value different than specified</e>
  <e id="5004">The key does not exist on the server</e>
  <e id="5005">An empty key was passed to an operation. Most commands do not accept empty keys.</e>
  <e id="5006">Timeout exceeded for operation. Inspect network conditions or increase the timeout.</e>
  <e id="5007">Server is under heavy load. Try again later.</e>
  <e id="5100">TOURNAMENT_NOT_FOUND</e>
  <e id="5101">TOURNAMENT_INVALID_ARG</e>
  <e id="5102">TOURNAMENT_INVALID_STATE</e>
  <e id="5103">TOURNAMENT_FAILED_AUTO_ADD</e>
  <e id="5104">TOURNAMENT_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="5105">TOURNAMENT_MAX_ENTRANTS</e>
  <e id="5106">TOURNAMENT_NO_ENTRANT</e>
  <e id="5107">TOURNAMENT_NO_MATCH</e>
  <e id="5108">TOURNAMENT_NOT_REGISTERED</e>
  <e id="5109">TOURNAMENT_INVALID_REGISTRATION</e>
  <e id="5110">TOURNAMENT_ALREADY_REGISTERED</e>
  <e id="5111">TOURNAMENT_ALREADY_BOUND</e>
  <e id="5112">TOURNAMENT_OPERATION_DENIED</e>
  <e id="6000">An error has occurred. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="6001">RPC_NO_LAYER</e>
  <e id="7000">All purchases are currently disabled.

Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="7001">An additional action is required to complete this transaction.

Go to Account Management to add more funds or to set up a payment method, and try again.</e>
  <e id="7002">An error has occurred. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="7003">Your transaction has timed out. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="7004">You have a pending transaction. Please try again once that transaction completes.</e>
  <e id="7005">Your account is currently not eligible to make this purchase.</e>
  <e id="7006">Your account is currently disallowed from making any purchases.</e>
  <e id="7007">An additional action is required to complete this transaction.

Go to Account Management to add more funds or to set up a payment method, and try again.</e>
  <e id="7008">An additional action is required to complete this transaction.

Go to Account Management to add more funds or to set up a payment method, and try again.</e>
  <e id="7009">An additional action is required to complete this transaction.

Your credit card has expired. Go to Account Management to update your credit card information, and try again.</e>
  <e id="7010">The information you entered was incorrect.</e>
  <e id="7011">DUPLICATE_REQUEST</e>
  <e id="7012">An error has occurred. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="7013">An error has occurred. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="7014">The product transaction was not valid for the specified client</e>
  <e id="7015">Timed out while waiting for the client to complete the purchase</e>
  <e id="7016">An error has occurred. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="7017">An error has occurred. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="7018">An error has occurred. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="7019">An error has occurred. Please try again.</e>
  <e id="7020">Purchases with real money are currently disabled.

Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="7021">You have a pending transaction. Please try again once that transaction completes.</e>
  <e id="7022">A pending transaction was canceled before the purchase was attempted.</e>
  <e id="7023">The Battle.net account was denied purchase access.</e>
  <e id="7024">You have reached the maximum spending limit for this alpha and cannot make additional purchases at this time.</e>
  <e id="7025">The payment service is currently under heavy load. Please try your purchase again later.</e>
  <e id="7026">This account has been blocked from purchasing by parental controls.</e>
  <e id="7027">The product catalog could not be downloaded from Battle.net.</e>
  <e id="7028">The license catalog could not be downloaded from Battle.net.</e>
  <e id="7029">The licenses were loaded but are currently out-of-date, purchases will be disabled until licenses can be loaded successfully.</e>
  <e id="7030">You already own this product.</e>
  <e id="8000">GPP_INTERNAL_ERROR</e>
  <e id="8001">GPP_DUPLICATE_TRANSACTION</e>
  <e id="8002">An error has occurred when attempting to purchase this item with gold. Please try again later.</e>
  <e id="8003">GPP_UNKNOWN_TRANSACTION_ID</e>
  <e id="8004">GPP_INVALID_TRANSACTION</e>
  <e id="8005">GPP_TRANSACTION_ID_IN_USE</e>
  <e id="8006">GPP_UNKNOWN_BATTLENET_ACCOUNT</e>
  <e id="8007">GPP_INVALID_REVOKE</e>
  <e id="8008">GPP_INVALID_STATUS</e>
  <e id="8009">GPP_TRANSACTION_REVOKED</e>
  <e id="9000">ROUTE_UNKNOWN_ERROR</e>
  <e id="9001">ROUTE_SERVICE_SEND_FAILURE</e>
  <e id="9002">ROUTE_CLIENT_SEND_FAILURE</e>
  <e id="9003">ROUTE_INVALID_FRAME_TYPE</e>
  <e id="9004">ROUTE_INVALID_FRAME_TYPE</e>
  <e id="9005">ROUTE_INVALID_PAYLOAD</e>
  <e id="9006">ROUTE_MISSING_CLIENT_ROUTER</e>
  <e id="9007">ROUTE_NO_ROUTE</e>
  <e id="9008">ROUTE_NO_NODE</e>
  <e id="9009">ROUTE_NO_HANDLER</e>
  <e id="9010">ROUTE_NO_DECODER</e>
  <e id="9011">ROUTE_NO_CLIENT</e>
  <e id="9012">REPLY_TIMEOUT</e>
  <e id="9013">INVALID_NUMBER_OF_TARGETS</e>
  <e id="9014">ROUTE_NO_REPLY</e>
</locale>